#### Contact

aadya.2727@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aadya-mishra27 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Composite Materials UAV system design Structural Dynamics

Languages

Hindi

English

# Aadya Mishra

Assistant Professor at CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY/ Aerospace Engineer (UAV)

Mohali

# Summary

No one is good at everything. As much as you may be in command of your core offering, chances are your messaging doesn't quite make the grade.

I'm an Aerospace Engineer with specialization in Unmanned Aerial Vehicle.

- --I am a multi-linguist of technology in Aerospace Industry.
- -- I have big ideas.
- --I don't care who gets credit. I just want to win.
- --I'm the calm one.
- --I run toward fires.
- --I like to make professional acquaintances.

Specialties: Good in - Aerodynamics, Aircraft Structure and Structural Dynamics, Finite Element Methods, Aeroelasticity, Performance Stability and Control of Aircraft, Composite Materials, UAV system Design.

# Experience

CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

Assistant Professor September 2018 - Present (2 years)

Mohali, Punjab, India

Indian Institute of Science (IISc) Research Intern June 2016 - May 2017 (1 year)

Bangaon Area, India

# Education

## University of Petroleum and Energy Studies

Master of Technology (MTech), Aerospace with specialization in Unmanned Aerial Vehicles (UAV) · (2015 - 2017)

### SCE Bangalore

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Aeronautical Engineering · (2011 - 2015)

#### TATA D.A.V. Public School

Higher School Secondary Certificate, General Science · (2009 - 2011)

#### Sacred Heart Convent School

Secondary School Certificate (Matriculation), general science · (1997 - 2009)